jonti2.co.za 2016-12-31

# Jonti 2

Your privacy is important and we respect this in the following policy:

  * From time to time, you may be asked to submit personal information about yourself (eg name and contact details) in order to receive or use our services. Your ability to choose any of our services is entirely voluntary. In addition, you can let us know at any time that you no longer wish to receive such services and you will be removed from our database.
  * We will not share, sell, rent, or trade your personal information with anyone outside of our organisation unless compelled to do so by law.
  * We are committed to protecting the integrity, confidentiality and privacy of the personal information you submit or share with us.
  * Thus, we us reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure. We will also use reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy policy and will take prompt corrective action when it learns of any failure to comply with our privacy policy. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties, which may inadvertently receive your information.
  * Our web server automatically collects website usage information from you when you visit our website. This is done on an anonymous basis. Such information informs us about how our visitors and candidates use and navigate our websites, including the number and frequency of users to each web page, their IP address, and the length of their stays. This is kept strictly company confidential and may only be used to improve our websites and or our Internet services.
  * Links within this portal to other websites are not covered by this policy and we are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such website to determine how that website protects your privacy.

**Destruction Policy**

In the event that you request to have your details removed from our database kindly take note of the following:

  * All data linked to you will be deleted including attached documents and cv’s
  * You details will not be searchable by client and no communication to you regarding future job opportunities will occur
  * All historical information related to you will be removed including screening and shortlisting information
  * In the event that the database has already been handed to the client we will inform the client to remove your details.
